scrapu.com 2010-12-29

# Privacy Policy Orkut Scraps Facebook Comments Hi5 Graphics

Thank you for visiting www.scrapu.com. By using the site, you are accepting the practices described in this privacy policy. These practices may be changed, but any changes will be posted and changes will only apply to activities and information on a going forward, not retroactive basis. You are encouraged to review the privacy policy whenever you visit the site.

 **Collection of Information -**  
We collect personally identifiable information, like email addresses, ONLY when voluntarily submitted by our visitors. This information is only used to fulfill your specific request (for example to add you to our mailing lists).

 **Cookie/Tracking Technology** -  
We use Google as third-party advertising vendor to serve ads when you visit our website. Please note that -

  * Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site.
  * Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on their visit to our site and other sites on the Internet.
  * Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

The advertising Vendor(s) may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/).

 **Commitment to Data Security -**  
Your voluntarily submitted personally identifiable information is kept secure. Only authorized employees, and contractors like Google Feedburner, who have agreed to keep information secure and confidential, have access to this information. All emails and newsletters from this site allow you to opt out of further mailings.
